Well, you just never know what
life has in store for you.
Indeed. Permission to meet him
alone was a surprise to me,
but if things go well,
His Majesty will consider the
request for a magic tutor.
Impressive power of collusion!
That's not what this is.
Apparently, the Royal Sorcerers
took an interest in you.
What kind of magic did you learn recently?
A-ori.
Wow! A cat. It's a cat!
Initially it was transparent,
but now I can even do white or calico.
Is this really water?
Yes.
Magic sure is a wonder.
Some motions are still unnatural,
but I want to study more and am
hoping to reproduce their meows.
Oh, there, there.
You like cats that much?
Well, no.
Why not keep a real cat?
Absolutely not!
If something like this was at home,
I'd never get any work done!
If you leverage the wealth
and power of the Gurions,
I'm sure you can collect cute
cats from all over the world.
We will not keep any
animals in our household.
We can't have them running around
your feet and making you trip.
But you needn't worry about me anymore.
And Tina prefers dogs.
I understand.
You are thinking of our family.
Thank you very much, Father.
No need to thank me.
Then how about keeping cats outside?
Iko told me that keeping cats outside is
a sign of a certain status among nobles,
and apparently bringing them
inside is considered crude.
Did she really mean cats?
Coming from that maid, I wonder...
Princess Mirika agreed.
Her Highness?
Yes.
Then maybe it's really about cats.
Cats!
Keeping cats outside...
Hmm, may not be a bad idea.
OFF TO THE CASTLE
Hello, Lord Gurion.
Oh, Lady Raysha.
Thank you for coming to greet us.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kunon Gurion.
I'm honored to meet you, my lady.
Lady Raysha is the second princess,
so greet her properly!
Oh, then you're my future sister-in-law!
I'm so happy to see you!
Nice to meet you, Kunon.
I'm Raysha Hughlia.
Mirika has told me so much about you.
By the way, you brought a cat.
How adorable!
Ah, this is...
I had no idea!
It's magic.
I didn't even name him...
He's more skilled than I'd heard.
How fleeting it was.
Then I shall take Kunon
to the Black Tower.
Thank you.
I will have an audience with His Majesty.
How will you get home?
I can get home by myself.
I'd like to see Her Highness, too.
Very well.
I'll arrange a carriage for you,
so enjoy your time.
Thank you.
I actually reserved an
auspicious restaurant,
the one where Father managed
to win Mother over.
That's quite enough!
Go and have fun!
Oh, my.
The Black Tower is on the
other side of the castle.
Are you comfortable walking?
Yes, I'm perfectly fine.
Then listen while we walk.
About the essence of sorcerers?
Not quite, since I'm still new.
A new interpretation of
compound magic, then?
Oh, the way to apply the old
interpretation to the new one?!
Wait, could it be the new theory on
three-dimensional and
oblique magic circles?!
Wait, wait, wait!
I can't have such high-level
conversations while walking.
Oh, right.
I trust you've heard from Mirika
that there are seven princes
and ten princesses?
The higher ratio of girls is wonderful.
The throne goes to the first
prince in most countries,
but in Hughlia we lean toward meritocracy.
So, depending on achievement,
birth order can be overturned.
I've heard that it's complicated.
Indeed.
I, however, relinquished my right
to the throne to be a sorcerer.
I sense so many magical powers.
What kind of sorcerers are there?
Mirika is
concerned that you might get dragged
into the issue of royal succession.
Huh?!
What's that?! What is that?!
I created a very thin layer of
water on my shoes and froze it.
Froze a very thin layer of water?
It's like an ice sleigh.
It's faster than walking.
Would you like to try?
Yes!
Hold on! I must tell you
before we do anything else.
If you put your weight on it,
it creates friction and—
Okay, I'll make it quick!
Don't affiliate with a faction carelessly,
and don't sign or say anything
that can be used against you.
Okay, that's it!
Now, let me skate, too!
Very well. I'd like to skate
with a beautiful lady like you.
Oh, my gosh!
Watch out!
This is amazing!
The trick is to float just a little.
Wh-What the?!
Please stop, Lady Raysha!
It's dangerous!
N-No good. They're too fast.
What in the world is going on?
Sir Dario!
You there!
Stop at once!
He's telling us to stop.
No way.
Go faster! Faster!
Stop... right now!
We're very sorry.
What's the commotion?
A child sorcerer made mischief
and got caught by a knight.
Welcome, Kunon Gurion.
I'm Londimonde Achthard, the Grand
Master of the Royal Sorcerers.
I'm Kunon Gurion.
Incredible.
I thought Lady Raysha's
magic was impressive,
but his is on a whole different level.
I hear you have a water crest.
Yes, on my left shoulder.
A two-star, huh?
A two-star?
FIRE, WATER, EARTH, WIND,
LIGHT, DARKNESS, FOUL
There are seven types of
crests borne by sorcerers:
fire, water, earth, wind,
light, darkness, and foul.
Each crest has five ranks.
Five... Then I assume mine is water,
second from the bottom?
Yes. Statistically, two-stars
are the most common.
I'm also a two-star, of the wind.
Is that so?
But you're not, correct?
What makes you think that?
The density of your magical
power is completely different.
An interesting description.
Right. If the magical powers of Lady
Raysha and I are regular cheese,
yours is like premium blue cheese.
That sounds stinky.
Not that I mind,
since it goes well with wine.
Grand Master Blue Cheese
is a three-star, perhaps?
I'll be mad if you call me that again.
I am... this.
A four-star.
You're not surprised?
This is my first time hearing about
crests, so it's not really sinking in.
Right. You'll get it eventually.
Grand Master.
Yes?
Does the difference in ranks
influence the magic one can wield?
There's no clear categorization.
The only clear distinction we know of
is the total amount of magical power.
What matters is what you'll learn
from now and how devoted you are.
I understand.
Well, then, can we move on?
Yes. Thank you for your time.
Then let the fun time begin!
Huh?
I am fascinated by you.
Let me give you a test.
He's amazing! Already amazing!
That's not fair. You've already seen it?
Seen it? I've experienced it!
Oh, I am very jealous!
Wait, is that the Hero's
Scar by any chance?
He's still a child.
He gave none other than
Sir Dario a hard time.
I'm interested to see what
kind of magic he uses.
Does this mean a Royal Sorcerer can
come be my teacher if I pass the test?
Please begin.
Victo.
Yes, sir.
A-ori.
Now, Kunon.
Can you conquer these with your A-ori?
Conquer magic with magic?
A-ori.
Listen to me, Master Kunon.
This is magic to produce and
manipulate water. But...
A-ori.
It can also control water
that's already there.
Control water that's already there.
I've controlled water many times before.
But manipulating the water
another sorcerer created...
Is something the matter, Kunon?
He nonchalantly gave me an
assignment neither Miss Jenié
nor I could come up with!
A-ori!
I've never experienced water that resists!
Come to me.
Come!
That's enough!
Only two.
So this is a Royal Sorcerer.
Nicely done, Kunon.
You're very good, indeed!
I didn't expect him to
take any, Grand Master.
May I have this child?
What? Don't be silly.
Seriously, don't be silly.
Didn't you just get dumped
by your girlfriend?
Don't be silly.
What does that have to do with this?
You can't even look after yourself.
Don't be silly, please.
Everyone seems to want you.
Does that mean I passed the test?
Hmm.
Why don't we try a few more things?
I'd love to experience your magic, too.
Very well!
This is fun!
And this is the Grand Master of the
Royal Sorcerers with a four-star crest.
Let us try it, too!
Please switch with us!
That's right! Hurry and
let us do it, old man!
I feel like I'm looking at
something I'm not supposed to.
Kunon!
What's this? What is this?!
It's Supersoft-Body A-ori.
I encased water in a super soft
and super stretchy membrane.
Imagine how well you'll sleep
if you make a bed out of this!
It might help absorb the shock of a fall.
I haven't had this much fun
with a magic test in years.
If I increase the elasticity,
you can jump so high
that you can easily reach the
second floor of the castle.
Is that true?!
I'd love to try it!
No, you shouldn't, Kunon!
Show us any more magic, and you
won't be able to go home tonight.
We wouldn't want to let you go!
I'm sorry, but I have dinner with my fiancée.
Oh, that's a shame.
Kunon, you can make other
animals than cats, right?
Can you make humans as well?
Yes, I can. A-ori.
A water doll, huh?
Yes. But just like animals, their
movements are still imperfect.
Does that mean, if your magic allows,
it's possible to have humanlike motion
or make it move in ways humans can't?
Yes. I tried letting it fly
as an experiment, but...
It's not very pleasant to watch, is it?
It wasn't well received.
I'd like to see it!
Yes! Please show us, Kunon.
Yes, sir!
No!
I-Is that a person?!
Oh no!
We're very sorry...
It was Victo who started it.
Don't be silly.
That's why you got dumped.
But you were all excited about it, too.
I got scolded twice today alone.
Feeling down isn't going
to change anything.
Next time, why don't we
discuss magic over lunch?
Next time? Does that mean I passed?
You saw how much fun I had,
so no need to ask.
I'll personally take care of assigning
a sorcerer to be your teacher.
Yes! Yes!
Will this imply I support a
specific royal faction?
No, don't worry.
Power and status mean
nothing to Royal Sorcerers.
Is that so? That's great!
For my information, I'd like to
ask if you have a future goal.
My goal is to create eyeballs with magic.
Oh yeah? That's impressive.
How intriguing.
That's nice. Very nice.
I've heard about my son's
bad reputation twice today.
What's the meaning of this?
I'm sorry, Father.
Kunon is not to blame.
We all got carried away.
I must disagree.
Regardless of the situation,
those who use magic should always be
held accountable for their actions.
Hurting someone because
they're told to do so.
Killing people because
they're ordered to do so.
Things like that should never be allowed.
Magic is power.
No matter who commands you,
refuse if it can bring harm to others.
As long as you wield power,
you are responsible.
Yes. I am very sorry.
But I'm surprised he stayed
this late in that tower.
Take care!
It seems you're in their
good books, Kunon.
Kunon, don't you have to go get Mirika?
Don't you have dinner?
What? Is it that late?
Yes, it's starting to get dark.
Oh, no!
It'd be so ungentlemanly of
me to greet Her Highness
all sweaty and out of breath!
True, then...
Let's combine our magic!
Huh?
A-ori.
Here we go.
I told you I had a wind crest.
If we fly this with my wind,
we can get to Mirika's in no time.
An interesting experiment,
but this is not good.
Huh?
I promised myself that
the first time I fly or float
alone with someone,
it'd be with Princess Mirika.
And I'm sure your fiancé
could misunderstand as well.
He'll blame you for
flying alone with a man.
Who cares?
Come on, get on!
I don't have a fiancé!
I've got no choice.
Let it float.
Yes, ma'am.
Ready to fly?
Isn't it too fast?!
So far, so good!
Let's go even faster!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
We're here, Kunon.
Thank you very much.
We made i—
Whoa?!
I'm grateful this is soft.
I am grateful this is soft.
I'm sorry. I should have gradually
decreased speed and altitude.
But now we know it can fly.
We need to experiment more.
You've done something dangerous again.
This is your third time.
We're very sorry.
Do you think Kunon will like this color?
It's Your Highness's favorite color.
I'm sure he'll be pleased.
Y-You think so?
To make Her Highness head
over heels like this...
What kind of a gentleman is Kunon Gurion?
First of all, Lady Raysha.
I must say that you lack awareness that
you are a part of the royal family.
You should be the one to respect rules...
NEXT EPISODE:
QUITE A BOY AND A NEW MASTER
Next episode: "Quite a
Boy and a New Master."